- Last summer when I was doing my internship
in Mongolia, I got a call from two classmates
in Tanzania.
They had a very urgent question.
How to use their washing machine
because all the labels were in Chinese
and Google kept translating a big button
as spinning ghost mode.
There we were, an Indian and the Thai calling me,
a Chinese, in Mongolia
to decipher a washer in Tanzania.
And we all studied together here at Harvard.
- The moment reminds me of something I used to believe
when I was a kid
that the world was becoming a small village.
I remember being told we will be the first generation
to end hunger and poverty for humankind.
My program at Harvard is International Development.
- Whoo! - Yeah!
- It was built on this exact beautiful vision
that humanity rises and falls as one.
When I met my 77 classmates
from 32 different countries,
the countries I knew only as colorful shapes on a map
turned into real people with laughter, dreams,
and the perseverance to survive the long winter.
In Cambridge.
- We danced through each other's traditions
and carried the weight of each other's walls.
Global challenges suddenly felt personal.
If there's a woman anywhere in the world
who cannot afford a period pad,
it makes me poor.
If a girl who skip school out of fear
of harassment, that threatens my dignity.
If a little boy dies in a war
that he didn't start
and never understood,
part of me dies with him.
But today, that promise of a connected world,
it's giving way to division,
fear and conflict.
We're starting to believe
those who think differently, vote differently,
will pray differently whether they are across the ocean,
or sitting right next to us, are not just wrong.
We mistakenly see them as evil.
But it doesn't have to be this way.
What I've gained most from Harvard isn't just calculus
or regression analysis,
is to sit - Whoo!
- with discomfort,
listen deeply,
and stay soft
in hard times.
Because if we still believe in a shared future,
let us not forget those who were labeled as enemies.
They too are human.
In seeing their humanity,
we find our own.
In the end,
we do not rise by proving each other wrong.
We rise by refusing
to let one another go.
So, class of 2025, when the world feels stuck
in spinning ghost mode,
just remember as we leave this campus,
we carry everyone we've met across wealth and poverty,
cities and villages, faith and doubt.
They speak different languages and dream different dreams,
and yet they've all become part of us.
You may disagree with them,
but hold on to them as we are bound
by something deeper than belief.
Our shared humanity.
Congratulations, class of 2025.