the Huawei MXT ultimate is probably the
most futuristic Flagship on this planet
right now and probably the largest leap
in smartphone Evolution since LG had
that crazy unit with the sideways
flipping screen may they rest in peace
this Smartphone has two hinges and three
screens making it the world's first
triple folding screen Smartphone when
fully extended the smartphone is nearly
the same size as an iPad I mean yeah it
does cost about $3,000 and for that
price you could probably duct tapee
three iPhones together and get almost
the same effect but there is a lot we
can learn about this new form factor and
with Huawei getting 65 million
pre-orders I'm sure there are a lot of
people with some very valid questions
about the long-term durability of their
future
device which is why I'm here right off
the bat we get the same warnings as all
the other folding phones like the Galaxy
fold and the Motorola Razor things like
don't remove the screen protector and
don't press too hard on the screen or it
might get damaged size-wise transforming
from iPad status back into its phone
form puts the M XT right about the same
size as my Galaxy s24 Ultra in a case
pretty mind-blowing to get so much
screen real estate in such a small
package the M XT can be a 6.4 in 8 in or
10.2 in display on a moment's notice and
when either of the two Wings get folded
in very strong magnets hold everything
into that closed position it's a bit
discombobulating at first knowing which
flat folds where and I'm a tad nervous
that it might break on accident before I
can break it on purpose I also have an
extremely bad feeling about the soft
folding screen being permanently Exposed
on the outside and more importantly that
same soft screen wrapping around the
exterior edge of the main Bend it's very
much unprotected all of the time the
exposed radius receiving even a small
impact from a drop or brush with metal
keys that are in the same pocket would
probably destroy the entire phone and
I'm not sure it can handle the same
abuse that our regular brick style
smartphone encounters on The Daily but
as you know we will find out for sure
what its limits are here in a few
minutes with a few of my specialized
tools and I might regret this but from
now until Christmas all of my Jerry rig
knives including the transparent Edition
are just $9.99 until they're gone all
the knives except for the 24 karat gold
plated version that'll stay expensive
for obvious reasons we're starting the
sale early this year to keep the
holidays a little less hectic for my
team which of course is incredibly easy
with my longtime Channel sponsor
stamps.com and their super simple
shipping see stamps.com lets any person
or business buy postage and ship
directly from their home or office using
just a computer and a printer holidays
are hectic and it's nice to have an
early start while avoiding the long
lines at the post office we ship the
knives in these recycled paper mailers
which even have padding on the inside
made from paper it's like a plastic
bubble mailer but actually recyclable
you can get up to 89% off ups and USPS
rates and seamlessly connect with every
major Marketplace and shopping car if
your small business is online doing so
all from your phone or computer day or
night no lines no traffic and no waiting
you can even schedule pickups and Order
shipping supplies through the stamps.com
dashboard more holiday less hustle you
can free up more time with stamps.com to
get your four-week trial free postage
and free digital scale just head to
stamps.com Jerri no long-term
commitments or contracts just how we
like it stamps.com
Jerri now when we get a screen that conf
Flex plastic is what we expect the only
way to verify though is with the most
scale of hardness using the level two
most pick which is also made from
plastic we start seeing some indentions
and deformations at a level two with
deeper grooves at a level three the
entire screen of the MXT ultimate both
inner and outer is fingernail
scratchable levels of plastic which of
course is not a deel breaker just good
information to have plastic is not
necessarily a bad thing but just like
you wouldn't hang drywall wearing a
Rolex or take a Lambo off-roading
actually that does sound kind of fun but
all I'm saying is as a daily driver the
M XT requires clean pockets and a bit of
extra attention the inner 8 megapixel
selfie camera which I won't touch with
my Razor is covered with that same soft
plastic with the screen turned off the
scratch marks from my fingernails and
plastic tools appear even more visual
ually apparent I don't want the soft
screen to distract from what a
phenomenal technological achievement
this phone has accomplished cuz for
reference if you remember Apple also
made their thinnest product ever this
year with the iPad Pro at 5.1 mm thick
this MXT ultimate clocks in at four it's
quite mindblowing to
hold the frame appears to be made from
aluminum including the hinge
nibblets the M XT does have stereo
loudspeakers the right side of the phone
has the metal volume rocker as well as a
side mounted fingerprint scanner inside
that power
button the three sides of the bottom
contain another loudspeaker a 66 W USBC
Port that's capable of 5w reverse wire
charging and a few microphones we do
have a SIM card tray which does have a
gray rubber ring around the opening but
no official IP or dust resistant rating
it's wild to see however that the
thickness of the physical USB cable that
I'm plugging into the phone is actually
thicker than the phone itself it's like
technology out of a science fiction
movie also there are rumors of a global
launch for this m XT ultimate in 2025
assuming of course that we're all still
here making our way over to the back the
only part of this phone that's thick is
the camera bump we have a 12 megapixel
Ultra wide camera in the top left corner
the main 50 megap variable aperture lens
is on the bottom and the 12 megap 5
times telephoto is in the upper right
with the laser autofocus below that all
all of which are sitting inside the star
Diamond designed Damascus steel looking
camera bump the red leather which I'm
not sure if it's real or not definitely
has a nice textured feel and the inlaid
Huawei branding and ultimate design
script won't be falling out or coming
out on its own there's a 50 W wireless
charging pad underneath this panel which
we might be lucky enough to see here in
a second the center panel is blank and
the far panel has a designed and crafted
by Huawei token embedded into the
leather the token is made from metal the
internally folding hinge similar to the
spine on Samsung's folding phone is made
from metal while the externally folding
hinge has the soft screen on the spine
which means I'm not going to scratch it
just yet the Damascus looking steel ring
around the camera units however is made
from metal the fully unfolded M XT
ultimate has a 3K resolution 90 HZ ltpo
OLED with 1 billion colors the blue J in
the background looks kind of like that
Twitter bird before it was murdered
under Flame the screen last for about 10
seconds before discoloring and the
surface layer literally melting huaw has
promised that the top layer of the
external screen is eligible for free
Replacements but the screen itself like
the pixel part of it if damaged outside
of warranty would cost about $1,100 to
fix which is surprisingly less than I
thought it would be now remember I do
not Delight in the destruction or
decimation of devices I'm just here to
eloquently educate on the endurance of
electronics where Norm normally if a
regular smartphone got accidentally
covered in sand it wouldn't be the end
of the world there might be some micr
scratches or abrasions on the glass from
the quartz or other hard minerals in the
aggregate but it would ultimately be
fine on a folding phone though
especially one as premium and finely
tuned as this one sand is a death
sentence not from the folding screen
itself now surprisingly that's still
alive and holding its own but the hinges
of the XT ultimate immediately fill up
with dirt and become unusable it's a
incredibly painful
sound I've been doing this dirt test on
folding phones for about 5 years now and
this is the worst grinding we've ever
encountered the hinge is so full even
after just a few pinches of sand that it
won't close anymore this $3,000 triple
folding smartphone is decidedly
decimated by a dash of
dirt going back to the exposed outer
radius of the soft folding screen Huawei
knows that is a weak point on the device
which is why they've included a
protective back panel case that flips up
to protect the exposed Edge definitely
nice protection is always a good thing I
am still curious though what would
happen if that bit of exposed screen did
get impacted during a drop or get
squeezed up against something in your
pocket using a tiny Pebble to press up
against the screen nothing happens I am
using quite a bit of force here but this
rock is small and the phone is still
unscathed and fully operational besides
some some cosmetic impressions in the
plastic however using my recently
discounted to 999 Jerry rig knife I can
tap the handle against the exposed Bend
and on the third strike with less Force
than it would have received during a
drop the inner pixels fracture and start
bleeding Black Ink in a Venom like
symbiote the ink permanently blemishes
the 3K resolution screen killing the
pixels underneath it is absolutely
imperative that the mate XT ultimate not
only stay away from dust but also never
never receive an impact on the front
unprotected flat display the M XT
ultimate is a marvelous Testament to
Modern engineering and an excellent
showpiece but it's definitely not ready
for the harsh environments of everyday
living one thing that wasn't immediately
intuitive is knowing which side folds
which direction especially since the
phone works in any orientation however
it appears as if Huawei has thought of
this as well and has introduced sensors
inside the phone to vibrate and notify
you if you're bending in the wrong
direction this is is the first
smartphone to ever beg for its life
during the bin test which almost makes
me want to give it a
chance the M XT ultimate can indeed be
catastrophically bent in the wrong
direction again worth repeating that a
device built for upscale eloquence
should be treated delicately with the
device dead it would be doing a
disservice if we didn't disassemble the
different divides the rear panel can
pretty much be pulled away without heat
exposing a battery in each of the
individual sections the main camera unit
segment doesn't come away quite as
easily but it
will the two batteries we have exposed
so far are the same size 1,930
milliamp with a bit more persuasion from
my Jerry rig knife the rear panel and
domastic steel camera lens housing does
come away from the
body revealing the absolutely beautiful
internals of the Huawei M XT Ultimate
dual folds triple batteries and if you
look closely you can see the variable
aperture camera open for one last time
the design is exquisitely complex it's
like seeing three phones get taken apart
for the price of three phones getting
taken apart the last battery we find
after unplugging the 50 W wireless
charging pad shows us the smallest of
the three
1,740 milliamp hours for a total of
5,600 is the Huawei M XT ultimate the
coolest phone on the planet today
probably yes is the Huawei M XT ultimate
durable most definitely not hit that
subscribe button and thanks a ton for
watching I'll see you around