- Last summer when I
was doing my internship
in Mongolia, I got a
call from two classmates
in Tanzania.
They had a very urgent question.
How to use their washing machine
(audience laughing)
because all the labels were in Chinese
and Google kept translating a big button
as spinning ghost mode.
(audience laughing)
There we were, an Indian
and the Thai calling me,
a Chinese, in Mongolia
to decipher a washer in Tanzania.
(audience laughing)
And we all studied
together here at Harvard.
(audience cheering)
(audience applauding)
- Yeah!
(audience cheering)
(audience applauding)
- The moment reminds me of
something I used to believe
when I was a kid
that the world was
becoming a small village.
I remember being told we
will be the first generation
to end hunger and poverty for humankind.
My program at Harvard is
International Development.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
(audience cheering)
(audience applauding)
- It was built on this
exact beautiful vision
that humanity rises and falls as one.
When I met my 77 classmates
from 32 different countries,
(audience cheering)
(audience applauding)
the countries I knew only
as colorful shapes on a map
turned into real people
with laughter, dreams,
and the perseverance to
survive the long winter.
In Cambridge.
(audience laughing)
- Whoo!
- We danced through
each other's traditions
and carried the weight
of each other's walls.
Global challenges suddenly felt personal.
(birds chirping)
If there's a woman anywhere in the world
who cannot afford a period pad,
it makes me poor.
(birds chirping)
If a girl who skip school out of fear
of harassment, that threatens my dignity.
(birds chirping)
(person cheering)
(audience cheering)
(audience applauding)
If a little boy dies in a war
that he didn't start
and never understood,
part of me dies with him.
(audience cheering)
(audience applauding)
But today, that promise
of a connected world,
it's giving way to division,
fear and conflict.
We're starting to believe
those who think differently,
vote differently,
will pray differently whether
they are across the ocean,
or sitting right next to
us, are not just wrong.
We mistakenly see them as evil.
(birds chirping)
But it doesn't have to be this way.
What I've gained most from
Harvard isn't just calculus
or regression analysis,
is to sit
- Whoo!
- with discomfort,
listen deeply,
and stay soft
in hard times.
Because if we still
believe in a shared future,
let us not forget those who
were labeled as enemies.
They too are human.
In seeing their humanity,
we find our own.
(audience applauding)
(audience cheering)
In the end,
we do not rise by
proving each other wrong.
We rise by refusing
to let one another go.
(birds chirping)
(audience applauding)
(audience cheering)
So, class of 2025, when
the world feels stuck
in spinning ghost mode,
(audience chuckling)
just remember as we leave this campus,
we carry everyone we've met
across wealth and poverty,
cities and villages, faith and doubt.
They speak different languages
and dream different dreams,
and yet they've all become part of us.
You may disagree with them,
but hold on to them as we are bound
by something deeper than belief.
Our shared humanity.
(birds chirping)
Congratulations, class of 2025.
(audience applauding)
(audience cheering)