---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the Huawei MXT ultimate is probably the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【most futuristic Flagship on this planet】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【right now and probably the largest leap】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【in smartphone Evolution since LG had】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【that crazy unit with the sideways】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【flipping screen may they rest in peace】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【this Smartphone has two hinges and three】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【screens making it the world's first】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【triple folding screen Smartphone when】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【fully extended the smartphone is nearly】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the same size as an iPad I mean yeah it】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【does cost about $3,000 and for that】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【price you could probably duct tapee】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【three iPhones together and get almost】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the same effect but there is a lot we】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【can learn about this new form factor and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【with Huawei getting 65 million】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【pre-orders I'm sure there are a lot of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【people with some very valid questions】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【about the long-term durability of their】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【future】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【device which is why I'm here right off】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the bat we get the same warnings as all】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the other folding phones like the Galaxy】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【fold and the Motorola Razor things like】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【don't remove the screen protector and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【don't press too hard on the screen or it】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【might get damaged size-wise transforming】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【from iPad status back into its phone】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【form puts the M XT right about the same】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【size as my Galaxy s24 Ultra in a case】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【pretty mind-blowing to get so much】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【screen real estate in such a small】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【package the M XT can be a 6.4 in 8 in or】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【10.2 in display on a moment's notice and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【when either of the two Wings get folded】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【in very strong magnets hold everything】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【into that closed position it's a bit】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【discombobulating at first knowing which】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【flat folds where and I'm a tad nervous】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【that it might break on accident before I】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【can break it on purpose I also have an】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【extremely bad feeling about the soft】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【folding screen being permanently Exposed】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【on the outside and more importantly that】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【same soft screen wrapping around the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【exterior edge of the main Bend it's very】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【much unprotected all of the time the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【exposed radius receiving even a small】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【impact from a drop or brush with metal】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【keys that are in the same pocket would】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【probably destroy the entire phone and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【I'm not sure it can handle the same】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【abuse that our regular brick style】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【smartphone encounters on The Daily but】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【as you know we will find out for sure】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【what its limits are here in a few】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【minutes with a few of my specialized】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【tools and I might regret this but from】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【now until Christmas all of my Jerry rig】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【knives including the transparent Edition】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【are just $9.99 until they're gone all】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the knives except for the 24 karat gold】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【plated version that'll stay expensive】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【for obvious reasons we're starting the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【sale early this year to keep the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【holidays a little less hectic for my】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【team which of course is incredibly easy】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【with my longtime Channel sponsor】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【stamps.com and their super simple】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【shipping see stamps.com lets any person】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【or business buy postage and ship】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【directly from their home or office using】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【just a computer and a printer holidays】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【are hectic and it's nice to have an】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【early start while avoiding the long】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【lines at the post office we ship the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【knives in these recycled paper mailers】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【which even have padding on the inside】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【made from paper it's like a plastic】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【bubble mailer but actually recyclable】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【you can get up to 89% off ups and USPS】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【rates and seamlessly connect with every】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【major Marketplace and shopping car if】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【your small business is online doing so】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【all from your phone or computer day or】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【night no lines no traffic and no waiting】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【you can even schedule pickups and Order】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【shipping supplies through the stamps.com】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【dashboard more holiday less hustle you】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【can free up more time with stamps.com to】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【get your four-week trial free postage】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【and free digital scale just head to】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【stamps.com Jerri no long-term】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【commitments or contracts just how we】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【like it stamps.com】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Jerri now when we get a screen that conf】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Flex plastic is what we expect the only】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【way to verify though is with the most】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【scale of hardness using the level two】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【most pick which is also made from】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【plastic we start seeing some indentions】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【and deformations at a level two with】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【deeper grooves at a level three the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【entire screen of the MXT ultimate both】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【inner and outer is fingernail】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【scratchable levels of plastic which of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【course is not a deel breaker just good】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【information to have plastic is not】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【necessarily a bad thing but just like】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【you wouldn't hang drywall wearing a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Rolex or take a Lambo off-roading】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【actually that does sound kind of fun but】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【all I'm saying is as a daily driver the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【M XT requires clean pockets and a bit of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【extra attention the inner 8 megapixel】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【selfie camera which I won't touch with】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【my Razor is covered with that same soft】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【plastic with the screen turned off the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【scratch marks from my fingernails and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【plastic tools appear even more visual】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【ually apparent I don't want the soft】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【screen to distract from what a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【phenomenal technological achievement】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【this phone has accomplished cuz for】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【reference if you remember Apple also】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【made their thinnest product ever this】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【year with the iPad Pro at 5.1 mm thick】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【this MXT ultimate clocks in at four it's】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【quite mindblowing to】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【hold the frame appears to be made from】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【aluminum including the hinge】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【nibblets the M XT does have stereo】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【loudspeakers the right side of the phone】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【has the metal volume rocker as well as a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【side mounted fingerprint scanner inside】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【that power】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【button the three sides of the bottom】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【contain another loudspeaker a 66 W USBC】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Port that's capable of 5w reverse wire】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【charging and a few microphones we do】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【have a SIM card tray which does have a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【gray rubber ring around the opening but】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【no official IP or dust resistant rating】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【it's wild to see however that the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【thickness of the physical USB cable that】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【I'm plugging into the phone is actually】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【thicker than the phone itself it's like】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【technology out of a science fiction】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【movie also there are rumors of a global】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【launch for this m XT ultimate in 2025】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【assuming of course that we're all still】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【here making our way over to the back the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【only part of this phone that's thick is】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the camera bump we have a 12 megapixel】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Ultra wide camera in the top left corner】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the main 50 megap variable aperture lens】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【is on the bottom and the 12 megap 5】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【times telephoto is in the upper right】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【with the laser autofocus below that all】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【all of which are sitting inside the star】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Diamond designed Damascus steel looking】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【camera bump the red leather which I'm】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【not sure if it's real or not definitely】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【has a nice textured feel and the inlaid】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Huawei branding and ultimate design】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【script won't be falling out or coming】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【out on its own there's a 50 W wireless】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【charging pad underneath this panel which】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【we might be lucky enough to see here in】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【a second the center panel is blank and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the far panel has a designed and crafted】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【by Huawei token embedded into the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【leather the token is made from metal the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【internally folding hinge similar to the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【spine on Samsung's folding phone is made】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【from metal while the externally folding】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【hinge has the soft screen on the spine】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【which means I'm not going to scratch it】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【just yet the Damascus looking steel ring】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【around the camera units however is made】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【from metal the fully unfolded M XT】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【ultimate has a 3K resolution 90 HZ ltpo】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【OLED with 1 billion colors the blue J in】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the background looks kind of like that】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Twitter bird before it was murdered】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【under Flame the screen last for about 10】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【seconds before discoloring and the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【surface layer literally melting huaw has】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【promised that the top layer of the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【external screen is eligible for free】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Replacements but the screen itself like】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the pixel part of it if damaged outside】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【of warranty would cost about $1,100 to】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【fix which is surprisingly less than I】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【thought it would be now remember I do】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【not Delight in the destruction or】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【decimation of devices I'm just here to】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【eloquently educate on the endurance of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【electronics where Norm normally if a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【regular smartphone got accidentally】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【covered in sand it wouldn't be the end】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【of the world there might be some micr】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【scratches or abrasions on the glass from】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the quartz or other hard minerals in the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【aggregate but it would ultimately be】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【fine on a folding phone though】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【especially one as premium and finely】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【tuned as this one sand is a death】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【sentence not from the folding screen】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【itself now surprisingly that's still】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【alive and holding its own but the hinges】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【of the XT ultimate immediately fill up】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【with dirt and become unusable it's a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【incredibly painful】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【sound I've been doing this dirt test on】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【folding phones for about 5 years now and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【this is the worst grinding we've ever】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【encountered the hinge is so full even】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【after just a few pinches of sand that it】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【won't close anymore this $3,000 triple】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【folding smartphone is decidedly】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【decimated by a dash of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【dirt going back to the exposed outer】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【radius of the soft folding screen Huawei】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【knows that is a weak point on the device】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【which is why they've included a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【protective back panel case that flips up】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【to protect the exposed Edge definitely】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【nice protection is always a good thing I】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【am still curious though what would】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【happen if that bit of exposed screen did】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【get impacted during a drop or get】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【squeezed up against something in your】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【pocket using a tiny Pebble to press up】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【against the screen nothing happens I am】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【using quite a bit of force here but this】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【rock is small and the phone is still】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【unscathed and fully operational besides】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【some some cosmetic impressions in the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【plastic however using my recently】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【discounted to 999 Jerry rig knife I can】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【tap the handle against the exposed Bend】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【and on the third strike with less Force】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【than it would have received during a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【drop the inner pixels fracture and start】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【bleeding Black Ink in a Venom like】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【symbiote the ink permanently blemishes】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the 3K resolution screen killing the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【pixels underneath it is absolutely】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【imperative that the mate XT ultimate not】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【only stay away from dust but also never】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【never receive an impact on the front】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【unprotected flat display the M XT】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【ultimate is a marvelous Testament to】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【Modern engineering and an excellent】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【showpiece but it's definitely not ready】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【for the harsh environments of everyday】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【living one thing that wasn't immediately】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【intuitive is knowing which side folds】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【which direction especially since the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【phone works in any orientation however】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【it appears as if Huawei has thought of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【this as well and has introduced sensors】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【inside the phone to vibrate and notify】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【you if you're bending in the wrong】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【direction this is is the first】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【smartphone to ever beg for its life】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【during the bin test which almost makes】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【me want to give it a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【chance the M XT ultimate can indeed be】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【catastrophically bent in the wrong】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【direction again worth repeating that a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【device built for upscale eloquence】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【should be treated delicately with the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【device dead it would be doing a】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【disservice if we didn't disassemble the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【different divides the rear panel can】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【pretty much be pulled away without heat】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【exposing a battery in each of the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【individual sections the main camera unit】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【segment doesn't come away quite as】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【easily but it】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【will the two batteries we have exposed】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【so far are the same size 1,930】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【milliamp with a bit more persuasion from】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【my Jerry rig knife the rear panel and】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【domastic steel camera lens housing does】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【come away from the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【body revealing the absolutely beautiful】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【internals of the Huawei M XT Ultimate】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【dual folds triple batteries and if you】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【look closely you can see the variable】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【aperture camera open for one last time】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the design is exquisitely complex it's】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【like seeing three phones get taken apart】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【for the price of three phones getting】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【taken apart the last battery we find】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【after unplugging the 50 W wireless】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【charging pad shows us the smallest of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【the three】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【1,740 milliamp hours for a total of】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【5,600 is the Huawei M XT ultimate the】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【coolest phone on the planet today】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【probably yes is the Huawei M XT ultimate】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【durable most definitely not hit that】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【subscribe button and thanks a ton for】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---
---BLOCK_START---TRANSLATE_TEXT_BELOW:【watching I'll see you around】END_OF_TEXT_TO_TRANSLATE. REPLACE_THIS_WHOLE_BLOCK_WITH_TRANSLATION---BLOCK_END---